rBuilder
User-guide CLI walkthrough · ecommerce-java
discover
Index the repo: graph + reachability + CFG/PDG
gql
Exact graph inventory — compact JSON for agents
gql (CALLS)
Who calls clearCart? Relation query, not grep
communities
Named communities — GQL overlay + communities list
blast-radius
What breaks upstream if I change CartService::clearCart?
blast-radius -f json
Same answer as structured metrics for CI / agents
metrics --pagerank
Architectural hotspots on the call graph
inspect
CFG for checkout — control-flow inside one function
slice
Backward slice: which lines influence item at addItem:53?
semantic index
Opt-in Hamming index (vocab = offline, no ONNX)
semantic query
Natural-language search over functions (fusion on by default)
semantic --scope community
Pool member embeddings — find subsystems by theme
export
Filter syntax (not GQL): name:clearCart → Mermaid subgraph
export (preview)
Show the Mermaid subgraph
check
CI gate: blast-radius policy on changed symbols